export const responses = [
  {
    name: "Jhon Doe",
    id: 1,
    status: "hired",
    dateHired: new Date(),
    deadline: new Date(),
    price: "£3000",
    answered: "No answer",
    lead: {
      id: 1,
      name: "Jane Doe",
      service: "Web Development",
      location: "New York, USA",
      budget: "$2,000",
      jobDescription: "Build a responsive website for an e-commerce store.",
      selected: true,
      responses: 2,
      price: 33,
      phone: "077*******",
      email: "J**********@gmail.com",
      details: [
        {
          question: "What are your website needs?",
          answer: "To sell products/services e.g. e-commerce",
        },
        {
          question: "What type of business is this for?",
          answer: "Sole trader/self-employed",
        },
        {
          question: "What industry do you operate in?",
          answer: "Creative industries",
        },
        {
          question: "When would you like the website to go live/be updated?",
          answer: "As soon as possible",
        },
        {
          question: "What is your estimated budget for this project?",
          answer: "Less than £250",
        },
        {
          question: "How likely are you to make a hiring decision?",
          answer: "I'm definitely going to hire someone",
        },
      ],
    },
  },
  {
    name: "Julia Dowson",
    id: 2,
    status: "pending",
    dateHired: new Date(),
    deadline: new Date(),
    price: "£3000",
    answered: "Started",
    lead: {
      id: 3,
      name: "Julia Dowson",
      service: "Social Media Marketing",
      location: "London, UK",
      budget: "$800",
      jobDescription:
        "Run a targeted social media campaign for a small business.",
      responses: 1,
      price: 33,
      phone: "077*******",
      email: "A**********@gmail.com",
      details: [
        {
          question: "What is your web design requirement?",
          answer: "Create a new website",
        },
        {
          question: "What are your website needs?",
          answer: "To advertise my business/services",
        },
        {
          question: "What type of business is this for?",
          answer: "Personal project",
        },
        {
          question: "What industry do you operate in?",
          answer: "Business services",
        },
        {
          question: "When would you like the website to go live/be updated?",
          answer: "As soon as possible",
        },
        {
          question: "What is your estimated budget for this project?",
          answer: "£1,000 - £1,999",
        },
        {
          question: "How likely are you to make a hiring decision?",
          answer: "I'm ready to hire now",
        },
      ],
    },
  },
  {
    name: "Jhon Doe",
    id: 1,
    status: "hired",
    dateHired: new Date(),
    deadline: new Date(),
    price: "£3000",
    lead: {
      id: 1,
      name: "Jane Doe",
      service: "Web Development",
      location: "New York, USA",
      budget: "$2,000",
      jobDescription: "Build a responsive website for an e-commerce store.",
      selected: true,
      responses: 2,
      price: 33,
      phone: "077*******",
      email: "J**********@gmail.com",
      details: [
        {
          question: "What are your website needs?",
          answer: "To sell products/services e.g. e-commerce",
        },
        {
          question: "What type of business is this for?",
          answer: "Sole trader/self-employed",
        },
        {
          question: "What industry do you operate in?",
          answer: "Creative industries",
        },
        {
          question: "When would you like the website to go live/be updated?",
          answer: "As soon as possible",
        },
        {
          question: "What is your estimated budget for this project?",
          answer: "Less than £250",
        },
        {
          question: "How likely are you to make a hiring decision?",
          answer: "I'm definitely going to hire someone",
        },
      ],
    },
  },
];
